It's the FC Bank, Rail, TCS, Lemon Tree,
ICICI, Lombard among stock in focus this
week. Here's why. Global credit rating
agency modist rating has revised the
outlook on serum finance to positive
from stable while affirming it is the
ball one long comes corporate final
rating
Reliance Industries this year SDFC bank
ICICI bank info says HCL technologies
zero financial
service we pro
bank and others will post their
quarterly result in the coming week.
Domestic equity benchmarks and sex and
conclude the first full week of 2026
with notable losses sliding more than 2%
there weekly decline since September
2025.
M highlighting global lyrics
and
present geopoliticals and
micronomics presses.
Here are a few stock that are likely to
be in focus next week.
SDFC Bank Rail DCS Lemon Tre ICICI
Lumbort among stock in focus next week's
hairs while global credit rating agency
mod and trading has revised the outlook
on serum finance to positive from stable
while a farming it by one long-term
corporate family rating
industries this year ICI
bank infoses HCL technologies This is
your financial service we prob and
others will post
quarterly result in the coming week.
Domestic equity benchmark Sensex and the
Nifty conclude the first full week of
2026 with notable losses each sliding
more than 2%
their steps weekly decline since
September 2025 and heighting global
risks evolution and precedent
geopolitical and micronics pressure.
Here are a few stock that are likely to
be in focus next week.
SDFC banker rail TCS lemon tree ICICI
lumbar among stock in focus next week's
hair choice global credit rating agency
mod the rating has revised the outlook
on serum finance to positive from stable
while affirming It is the B one long
terms corporate family
Reliance industry
TCSC bank ICL
bank then HCL technologies z
service prob and others will post their
quarterly result in the coming week
domestic equity benchmarks and sex and
Nifty conclude the first full week of
2026 with notable losses is sliding more
than 2% steps weekly decline since
September 2025 am heightings global risk
ever and
president on geopolitical and
micronomics project